http://www.lumitex.com/privacy-policy/

Last Modified: May 25, 2018
Lumitex is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy governs data collection and usage for our website and services. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the website or services.
Website Images
All Images are protected as All Rights Reserved. To request permission to use images on www.lumitex.com please email marketing@lumitex.com.
Collection of your Personal Information
You are free to explore the Website without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you visit the Websites, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information. Lumitex collects personal information that you voluntarily submit to us and identifies you personally, such as your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address and/or telephone number. Lumitex also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Lumitex. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Lumitex for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Lumitex website.
In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Lumitex public message boards or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Lumitex is not obligated to read your online communications with others.
Lumitex encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Lumitex so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Lumitex is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside our family of websites or the use of your information by such outside websites.
Use of your Personal Information
Lumitex collects and uses your personal information to operate our website and deliver the services you have requested. We may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Lumitex and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.
We do not sell, rent or lease our customer lists to third parties. Lumitex may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Lumitex, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Lumitex does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. Lumitex keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within our websites, in order to determine what services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Lumitex to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.
Our websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Lumitex or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Lumitex (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Lumitex, or the public.
Use of Cookies
Lumitex website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Lumitex pages, or register with our site or services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Lumitex website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the services or websites you visit.
If you provide us with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:
To review the user information that you have supplied to us
To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
To request that your user information not be used to contact you
To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
To request that your user information be deleted from our records and
To opt out of being solicited by this website or third parties
If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while we verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and/or limit your access to our website.
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the Contact Us page.
Security of your Personal Information
No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Lumitex uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Lumitex secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Lumitex periodically updates this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification.
Enforcement of this Privacy Policy
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at support@lumitex.com.
Unsubscribe From Lumitex
You may unsubscribe from Lumitex marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the company’s emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe by contacting Lumitex at support@lumitex.com.
Contact Information
Lumitex welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Lumitex has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Harness the Power of Light
Get latest illumination tips, updates and ideas delivered to your inbox!
Lumitex, LLC.
8443 Dow Circle Strongsville, Ohio 44136
Lumitex Asia, LLC 3F., No. 1, Aly. 17, Ln. 62, Zhonghe St. Zhubei City, Hsinchu County 302, Taiwan (R.O.C.)
Privacy Policy   Site Map
